daz3d.com 2011-05-28

# DAZ 3D - Free 3D Software and 3D Model Providers

## DAZ 3D Privacy Policy

* * *

_LAST UPDATED: 04/29/08_

#### The DAZ 3D Customer Privacy Policy

DAZ 3D's Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by DAZ 3D anytime you interact with DAZ 3D, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase DAZ 3D products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. Your privacy is a priority at DAZ 3D, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

#### Collection and Use of Your Personal Information

When you interact with DAZ 3D, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the DAZ 3D products you own, such as their serial numbers and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issues. 

We collect information regarding customer activities on our website. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and Internet services are of most interest to you.

We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve DAZ 3D's products.

If you use a bulletin board or any of the other publicly available portions of the DAZ 3D website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. DAZ 3D is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, DAZ 3D will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

Except as described in this statement, DAZ 3D will not disclose your personal information outside of DAZ 3D and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent. DAZ 3D does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

#### Security We Use to Protect Your Personal Information

DAZ 3D takes precautions - including administrative, technical, and physical measures - to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser.

Please [contact us](https://helpdaz.zendesk.com/home) if you have questions or concerns about DAZ 3D's Customer Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us by using our web form. The DAZ 3D Data Controller in your region will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

DAZ 3D may update its privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how DAZ 3D is protecting your information.

Copyright 2007-2008 DAZ Productions, Inc., dba DAZ 3D.
